-=蓝光电影网=-
blu-raydisc.tv
下载更多蓝光高清电影-3D电影
请到-=蓝光电影网=-
在Lompoc最高防备监狱服刑
at the Lompoc Maximum Security Prison system
不得假释
without the possibility of early parole.
这就是目前我们所了解的情况
Here's what we know so far.
这就是这次疯狂的白日越狱的惨烈后果
This is all the aftermath of a daring, daylight breakout.
有26名极度危险的服刑人员将被转狱
There were 26 high-risk inmates being transferred...
所有转狱的囚犯都已找到
A daring midday breakout where everyone on board has been accounted for,
除了一个人  Dominic Toretto
except for one, Dominic Toretto.
警方刚刚公布了嫌犯的身份信息
Police have just released the identity
据信他就是今天下午发生的惊天大脱狱的幕后主脑
of the man they believe to have orchestrated the shocking escape
幸运的是这次脱狱并没有造成人员伤亡
that amazingly resulted in no fatalities this afternoon.
他就是前联邦特工  Brian O'Conner
He is former federal agent, Brian O'Conner.
追捕三名逃犯的搜捕行动今晚将展开
A fierce manhunt is underway for three fugitives tonight.
联邦警察及当地警力已组成联合追捕小组
Multiple federal and local agencies have joined forces
全力搜捕Dominic Toretto
in the search for Dominic Toretto
以及其同伙Brian O'Conner  Mia Toretto
and his accomplices Brian O'Conner and Mia Toretto.
尽管布下了天罗地网
But despite every eye in the country looking for them
但Toretto 和 O'Conner依然如人间蒸发了一般
where Toretto and O'Conner are now is anyone's guess.
就是这儿了了 是不?
It's got to be it, right?
叽里呱啦的葡萄牙语
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
我们还是走吧  哇   哇
Let's get out of here. VINCE: Whoa, whoa!
继续叽里呱啦的葡萄牙语
(VINCE SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
淡定 兄弟
Easy, friends.
她是我的妞儿
She's with me.
Mia.
Vince.
狗杂种
Buster.
来吧
Come on.
Dom到了吗?
Dom here yet?
还没
No.
上一次你跟他联系是什么时候?
When was the last time you heard from him?
几周前 在Ecuador的什么地方
A couple of weeks ago. Up in Ecuador somewhere.
感觉怎么样?             什么怎么样?
VINCE: How does it feel? What's that?
出现在通缉令的另一面?
To be on the other side of a wanted poster?
他会现身的
He'll show up.
Yeah.
Dom的妹妹?
Dom's?
Yeah.
还在说叽里呱啦的葡萄牙语 （后面的葡语翻译都在下一句）
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
该睡觉觉了 小家伙
Time for bed little one.
我能带着他吗?
Can I bring him?
当然
Of course.
哦
MIA: Aw.
晚安
Good night.
不好意思
Excuse me, sorry.
为什么是里约  Vince?
Why Rio, Vince?
你的意思是在你在LA把一切都搞砸了过后
You mean after you screwed everything up in LA?
最后我们的逃亡穿越了整个南美洲
Ended up free-falling through South America, you know,
跌跌撞撞 狼狈不堪
hitting every hellhole on the way down.
要不是为了ROSA说不定还得继续逃亡
Would have kept on going if not for Rosa.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
他知道吗?
Does he know?
那么 听着
So, listen.
有活干了
There is a job coming up.
我本希望Dom这时候已经到了
I was hoping Dom was going to be here by now
但是现在很清楚 没他我们也能行
but this one is clean enough we can do it without him.
只是一件小活儿 几辆高端车  很容易得手
It's a good gig. Couple of high-end cars, easy targets.
现在我们只需要组个队来偷车车
Guy I know is putting together a team to swipe them.
还差几个人手
Just need a few more willing bodies.
我不知道
I don't know.
瞧  不管都干不干 车子就在那儿
Look, the way the car scene is down here
我们可以轻易的就给偷走   然后就数钱钱了
we can unload them quick and get top dollar.
不费吹灰之力
It's easy money.
在我看来
And from where I'm sitting,
看起来你们两个人都需要钱啊
it looks like you both could use the payday.
你在看啥书?
What are you reading?
旅游指南
Travel guide.
恩?
Yeah?
东京
Tokyo.
莫斯科
Moscow.
果阿（印度）
Goa.
想知道这些地方都有什么共同之处吗?
You want to know what all of these places have in common?
恩
Huh?
不用被引渡
No extradition.
开工了
Here we go.
不好意思 兄弟
Excuse me, buddy.
Okay.
嘿 我们找到那些车了
Hey, we've found them.
对 倒数第二节车厢
Yeah, second-to-the-last freighter.
是什么?
What is it?
DEA（美国毒品侦缉管理局）的标签 这些车被充公了的
DEA tags. These cars have been seized.
瞧瞧谁来了
Look who showed up.
神啊  看到你平安无事我就放心了
God, I'm so happy you're okay.
我想我跟你说过要低调点的
I thought I told you to lay low.
被追的踹不过起来     得做个决定了
Been running on fumes. Had to make a call.
嘿 别闲聊了  我们只有两分钟的时间
Hey! Quit talking. We only got the two-minute window.
动手吧 Vince
Let's go, Vince.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
GT40让我来
I'm taking the GT40.
女士优先
Ladies first.
嘿
Hey!
MIA: Hey!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
这辆车更衬我
This car suits me better.
回见 宝贝儿
See you, baby.
乖 不哭....  反正我们都是去同一个地方的
It's okay... we're all going to the same place.
到那儿再把车抢过来
We'll get the car there.
计划有变  等我的指示
Change of plans. Wait for my call.
动手!
Let's go!
她要去哪儿?
Where is she going?
她要去哪儿? 嘿!
Where is she going? Hey!
嘿!
Hey!
我们被抢啦!  不管发生什么 别停车!
We're being robbed! Whatever happens, don't stop the train!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
追那小妞!
Go after the girl!
快啊!
Hurry up!
拿门卡!    快拿门卡!
Access card! Get the access card!
妈妈的
Shit.
桥!  前面有座桥!
Bridge! There is a bridge!
行李车安全
Luggage car is clear.
不许动!
Freeze!
哦 完了!
Oh, Shit!
你要做决定  是吧?
You had to make a call, huh?
去你妈妈的决定  O'Conner
Shitty call, O'Conner.
去你妈妈的决定
Shitty call.
你俩今天惹的麻烦可够多的
You two stirred up quite a bit of trouble today.
我挂了三个手下
Three of my men dead.
还有三个DEA的特工也挂了
Three DEA agents along with them.
当然了 生意嘛
Of course, this is business
有点小波折是难免的
and sometimes things go astray.
我所关心的只有车
All I care about is the car.
告诉我车在哪儿 我就放你们走
Tell me where it is, and I'll let you go.
这屋顶的塑料都在笑你娃是满嘴跑火车
BRIAN: This roofing plastic says you're full of shit. (REYES LAUGHING)
我不知道你们那儿是怎么做生意的
I don't know how you guys do business in your part of the world,
但是在里约
but here in Rio,
我很乐意让所有人知道他们是在跟谁做对
I like it when all parties know what they're up against.
搞笑哦
DOM: That's funny.
因为两种方式都行哦
Because it goes both ways.
你懂得
You know,
我听说你妹妹长的很正
I hear your sister is very beautiful.
她藏到天涯海角
Wherever she hides
我也找得到她
I Will find her.
新闻联播也说的是葡萄牙语
(NEWSCASTER SPEAKINGPORTUGUESE)
美国逃犯在火车劫案中干掉了三名DEA特工
The American fugitives killed three DEA agents during a train robbery...
警方称其持械并且极度危险
...Police warn they are armed and extremely dangerous.
有关于逃犯的消息请立即与警方联系
Anyone with information should contact law enforcement immediately...
BRIAN: Mia?
Hey.
你没事吧?
You okay?
没事  你们都还好吧?
Yeah, you all right?
Hey.
Hey, yeah.
还是我们Toretto家人的样儿
Just like a Toretto.
Vince去哪儿呢?
Where's Vince?
问得好
That's a good question.
他会来的
He'll be here.
伙计们 新闻里都说的是咱们
Guys, we're all over the news.
他们说是我们杀了火车上的DEA的特工
They're blaming us for the Killing of those DEA agents on the train.
很显然现在我们就成了头号通缉犯了
Which means we just jumped to the top of the wanted list.
联邦调查局这回可要放手大干了
The feds have got to show everyone their agents are off limits
他们派精英了 我们得快点走了
and they're going to send their best guys. We got to get out of here.
有件事我们很肯定
One thing we know for sure
那就是他们想要这车
is that they wanted this car.
因为里面肯定有玄机
Because something is in it.
如果我们能找出来的话 我们就不那么被动了
If we find out what it is, we'll know what we're up against.
好了 都听好了 我们要抓的人都是职业车手
HOBBS: All right, listen up! The men we're after are professional runners.
他们喜欢飙车并且肯定不会轻易就范
They like speed and are guaranteed to go down the hardest possible way
所以不要到时候虾的尿裤子
so make sure you got your funderwear on.
我们找到他们 全部拿下 带回来
We find them, we take them as a team, and we bring them back.
重中之重  千万 千万 别让他们碰车
And above all else, we don't ever, ever let them get into cars.
罪案已经发生了有十个小时了 出发
Crime scene is 10 hours old and counting, men. Let's go hunting.
Hobbs特工 警察总长  João Alemeida来的电话
Agente Hobbs! Chief of Police, João Alemeida.
Luke.
很抱歉你的人牺牲了
Sorry to hear about the loss of your men.
为了抓这两个人值得吗?
Is all this really necessary to apprehend two men?
让我给你说道说道这两人吧
Let me tell you something about these two men.
其中一个是前联邦特工 卧底五年了
One is a former federal officer, been in deep cover for five years.
他对我们的运作方式了若指掌
He knows every way you're going to come for him.
另外一个是职业惯犯 已经脱狱两次了
The other one is a professional criminal, escaped prison twice,
他的大半生都在疲于奔命
spent half his life on the run avoiding folks like you.
那么有没有什么使我们可以帮到DSS的...
Well, if there's anything we can do to help the DSS...
两件事  一 我需要个翻译
Two things. One, I need a translator.
我们公关部多的是
We have plenty in the public relations department.
Elena Neves.
要个巡警? 你听清楚了的
A patrol officer? You heard me.
但为啥?  比她有经验的人我们多的是
But why? We have many more experienced people.
我喜欢她笑起来的样子
I like her smile.
第二件事呢?
What's the second thing?
好狗不挡道
Stay the fuck out of my way.
Brian. Hm?
有点事我得跟你说
I have something I have to tell you.
不是吧
VINCE: God damn.
真是一团糟!
What a mess!
你都去哪儿啦 兄弟?
Where you been, man?
你最好注意点说话的方式
You better check that tone.
你他妈的最好还是先回答我的问题
And you just better answer the goddamn question.
住手! 你们俩都住手
Stop it! Both of you.
你去哪儿呢 Vince?
Where were you, Vince?
整个贫民窟的人都在问起你
Guys all over the favelas asking about you.
不先把他们糊弄了就没办法离开
Couldn't get out of there without leading them straight to you.
得等他们都散开了才行
Had to wait them out.
真他妈妈的瞎胡扯
That is such horseshit
那是你接的活    那些人是你的伙计!  嘿!
That was your job,and those were your guys! Hey!
嘿!   够了 O'Conner!
Hey! Enough, O'Conner!
如果他说他没做过 那他就真没做过
If he said he didn't do it, he didn't do it.
去走走 消消气
Go walk it off.
瞧 我倒是想到你的国家来开展下业务
REYES: Look, I would love to expand my operations into your countries
但 坦白的说  你的操作方式太暴力了
but, quite frankly, your business methods are too violent.
我给你讲个真实的故事吧
Let me tell you a true story.
500年前  葡萄牙人和西班牙人都曾到过这里
Five hundred years ago, the Portuguese and the Spanish came here,
双方都想从当地土著手里夺取他们的国家
each trying to get the country from their natives.
西班牙佬来了  枪炮齐发 想证明他们才是老大
The Spaniards arrived, guns blazing, determined to prove who was boss.
当地土著对西班牙佬赶尽杀绝
The natives killed every single Spaniard.
所以  我个人还是比较喜欢葡萄牙人的方式
Personally, I prefer the methods of the Portuguese.
他们带着礼物而来
They came bearing gifts.
镜子 剪刀   小饰物
Mirrors, scissors, trinkets.
当地土著没法自己制作的东西
Things that the natives couldn't get on their own,
拿人手软    他们不得不为葡萄牙人工作
but to continue receiving them, they had to work for the Portuguese.
这就是为啥现在巴西人都说葡语的原因
And that's why all Brazilians speak Portuguese today.
所以 如果你用暴力的方式来统治他们
Now, if you dominate the people with violence,
他们终将会反抗的  因为他们已一无所有 无所畏惧了
they will eventually fight back because they have nothing to lose.
这就是关键
And that's the key.
现在我要去贫民窟 给他们的甜头了
I go into the favelas and give them something to lose.
电力  自来水
Electricity, running water,
给孩子们修学校
school rooms for their kids.
让他们感受点幸福生活
And for that taste of a better life,
是我欠他们的
I own them.
先生们
Gentlemen.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
很抱歉打断一下
I apologize for the interruption.
Reyes先生  我能跟你说句话吗?
Senior Reyes, may I speak with you?
我们找到他们了
We've found them.
不好意思 先生们
Pardon me, gentlemen.
真希望我没看见
DOM: Almost wish I didn't see that.
真的
Almost.
等等 Dom
Wait, Dom.
Mia在那火车上
Mia was on that train.
我妹!
My sister!
我也不知情的  我是不会伤害她的
I didn't know. I wouldn't do anything to hurt her.
但是是你主持的的交易
You set up the deal!
我以为就是偷车而已
I thought the job was for the cars.
我真不知道啊
I didn't know.
他们只是想要芯片
All they want is the chip.
去你妈的!
Damn!
你本该查清楚的
You should've come clean.
外面发生了什么事情?
What's going on out here?
没事儿
Nothing.
求你了 DOM 把芯片给我 我可以给他们送过去
Please, Dom, just let me have the chip. I can take this to them.
他们会转交给Reyes 然后就天下太平了
They'll give it to Reyes and set things right.
滚出去
Get out.
什么?
What?
滚出去!
Get out!
你从来都不听我说
You never listen to me.
在我告诉你他曾是个警察 你不听  现在你也不听
Not when I told you he was a cop, and not now.
你从来都不相信我  看看现在都咋样了吧
You never trust me and look where it's gotten us.
看看现在我们的家庭
Look at our family now.
我回不了家 !你妹现在也牵扯进来了!
I can't go home! Your sister is stuck in this life!
Letty在哪儿 Dom?
Where's Letty, Dom?
Letty在哪儿?
Where's Letty?
空气等离子切割机
Plasma cutter.
Wilkes 我要一张分布在五十英里范围内的
Wilkes, I want a list of every place within 50 miles
所有压缩气罐的清单
that distributes compressed gas tanks.
给我那张货运清单
Pass me that manifest.
Neves警官  等你很久了
Officer Neves. Been waiting for you.
你要见我? 是的
You asked for me? I did.
能告诉我原因吗?
May I ask why?
我的微笑还没那么有魅力
My smile is not that great.
你丈夫是一位在贫民窟被枪杀了的警官
Your husband was an officer who was gunned down in the favela.
6个月后 你加入了警队
Six months later, you upped and joined the force.
你是有动机的
You're motivated.
另外  我发现你是里约唯一不会被收买的人
Plus, I figure you're the only one in Rio who can’t be bought.
我说的没错吧?
Am I right?
是 我当然没错
Yes. Of course I am.
好消息 坏消息
Good news, bad news.
你知道我一向都喜欢先吃甜点(指先听好消息）
You know I like my dessert first.
按你的要求又检查了铁道线
Back-checked the rail line like you asked.
发现了几个他们下货的地方
Found a couple of spots where they unloaded the cars.
其中一条通向西面
One set of tracks headed west
直到上了主干道  然后他们就消失了
until it hit the main highway, then disappeared.
而另一条通向东面
But another set of tracks headed east.
107英寸的轴距   8寸半的轮胎
A 107-inch wheelbase, eight-and-a-half-inch tread.
那辆货单上消失了的GT40
The GT40 that was missing from the manifest.
跟着轨道跑了几英里
Followed the trail a couple of miles.
从这抓痕很容易辨别出来
Pretty easy in this scrub.
很难不留下痕迹
Can't move without leaving a sign.
再给我吃蔬菜吧(指坏消息)
Give me the damn veggies.
进入了硬路了  看不到痕迹    我们就跟丢了
The ground rolls into a hardpack and we lost that track, too.
也不尽然
Not necessarily.
那路通向山上然后再通向贫民窟
That road heads up through the hills into the favelas.
几年前 被一场大雨冲垮了
Couple of years ago, it was washed out by a storm.
从你到的地方过去一英里后全是泥路
It's all dirt a mile from where you were.
如果他们是朝那个方向去的   我们在那儿就可以发现他们的痕迹
If they headed that way, we'll pick up their tracks there.
你可真是有备而来
You come prepared.
我可是有动机的
I'm motivated.
那好吧
HOBBS: All right, then.
我们去找车吧
Let's find ourselves a car.
你怎么看?
What do you think?
恩 这肯定是个订制的芯片
Well, it's definitely a custom chip.
看看这些为了数据输入的侧菜单
Look at all these side menus here for data entry.
先看看这个
Let's check this one.
看那儿
Look at that.
同样的地点 每周相同的订单
Same building, same order every week.
这个是送货安排表
It's a delivery schedule.
这是啥?
What's this?
毒品?
Drugs?
不 是毒贩子的包裹
No. That's a dealer pack.
瞧 大多数的贩子  他们称钱
See, most major players, they weigh their money
这样他们就不用老是数钱了
so they don't have to constantly count it.
在这儿   一共49公斤
Right there, that's 49 kilos.
现在我们说的49KG是指一百万
49 kilos is a million in twenties.
你的意思是这些货物每个都价值一千万?
You're saying each one of these shipments is worth 10 million dollars?
Yeah.
靠谱
I thought so.
那么那是啥?
So what is that?
放在现金屋里的一亿美刀?
A 100-million plus in cash houses?
这就是他藏钱的方法
That's how he keeps it off the grid.
我现在敢说Reyes要要回这芯片是个明智之举
I think it's safe to say that Reyes is smart to want this back.
这就是他的整个生意网络 就在这芯片里
It's his whole network right there, just laid out on a chip.
Wilkes, Fusco  走中路
Wilkes, Fusco, up the middle.
Mac, Chato 走北面
Mac, Chato, flank north.
我呢?
What about me?
呆着
Stay here.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
走那边!
Go that way!
另外两人翻墙!
The other two went over the wall!
快 快走 快走
Come on, go! Go!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
趴下!
Get on the ground.
我抓住Toretto了 你在北面的四个街区....
I got Toretto. Four blocks north of your...
他们已经知道你的身份了
They already know who you are.
你大爷的用葡语大喊
(YELLING IN PORTUGUESE)
我们走
Let's go.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
你没事吧?
You okay here?
恩 我没事 谢谢
Yeah. I'm good. Thank you.
现在他们在搜捕待在一起的我们
They're going to be looking for the three of us together now.
我们得分开
We need to split up.
你和Mia走南面 我去把他们引开
You and Mia head south, I'll lead them away.
不要
No.
Dom说的对
Dom is right.
你看看刚才有多险   下次咋办?
Look how lucky we just got. What happens next time?
没得选 只有分头走
We have no choice but to split up.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
我曾失去过我的家庭
I already lost my family once.
我不愿再经受那种痛苦
I'm not going through that again.
你说真的?  真的
Are you kidding me? No.
我哪儿都不会去的 好不?
I'm not going anywhere. Okay?
Dom?
答应我 我们永远在一起
Promise me we stick together.
我答应你
I promise.
我们的家庭有添加了新成员了
Our family just got bigger.
说不通啊
Something doesn't add up.
Toretto and O'Conner.
该跑的时候不跑   他们偷了油然后又倒啦?
They stay when they're supposed to run, they steal gas then give it away?
现在他们又开始杀联邦特工啦?
Now they're killing federal agents?
没道理啊
It doesn't make any sense.
这里说的通
Here's what makes sense.
这些家伙的名字都在名单上
All these guys are is names on a list.
只要他们出现 我们就把他们放翻
They come up, we take them down.
不用多打电话 也不用少开一枪
Not a phone call more, not a bullet less.
Wilkes 有收获没有?
Wilkes, we get anything?
标准检验方式
Standard forensics.
鞋印  毛发  纤维
Shoe prints. Hair and fiber.
车上全是鞋印
Prints are all over the car.
还有没有其他线索?
Anything else?
有 我们追查到了车主信息
Yeah, we tracked the owner off the vehicle ID.
中间有几家是空壳公司
There are a couple of shell companies in between,
但我们最后还是查到有家公司
but we finally traced it back to a corporation
是由这里的一个叫Hernan Reyes所投资的
owned by an investor down here named Hernan Reyes.
投资人?
Investor?
只要在里约有什么非法交易 那就有Reyes他的份儿
If there’s anything illegal happening in Rio, Reyes is involved.
好吧 那么我们也是
Okay, then so are we.
如果他能帮我们抓住那些家伙   那么我要他的全部信息
If he could get us any closer to our guys, I want everything on him.
Chato  你上屋顶
Chato, you're on the roof.
我要你放哨 以防有人回来取东西
I want you on overwatch in case somebody comes back for something.
Mac 再帮我全方位的查查Reyes
Mac, give me a cross-check on Reyes, full specs.
就算是他是去尿尿 我也要知道他是怎么甩JJ的（女同胞不懂这段的问问男同胞）
If he goes to the john, I want to know how many times he shakes it.
收到 老大   Wilkes Fusco!
You got it, boss. Wilkes, Fusco!
我们来装车吧
Let's put all this mess back together.
那得花点时间
That's going to take a while.
那你还不开工
Then you better get started.
他们把这车给拆了是有原因的
They were taking this car apart for a reason.
我们把它装回去 看看都少了啥
Let's put it back together and find out what's missing.
嘿 Dom 你记忆中的父亲是什么样的?
Hey, Dom, what do you remember about your father?
我爹
My father.
他曾经...
He used to...
他曾每周日去教堂后都会弄烧烤
He used to have a barbecue every Sunday after church.
邀请所有的邻居来参加
For anybody in the neighborhood.
但你不去教堂的话 你就没得吃
If you didn't go to church, you didn't get any barbecue.
他在店里的每一天 每一夜
Every single day he was in the shop, and every single night,
他在厨房桌旁 给Mia辅导功课
he was at the kitchen table with Mia, helping her with her homework.
即便是在她睡着后
Even after she went to sleep,
他都还会再待几个小时
he'd stay up for a few more hours
预习下一课 以便第二天辅导她
so he could learn the next chapter and help her the next day.
我记得我父亲的一切
I remember everything about my father.
一切
Everything.
就这样
That's just it.
我一点不记得我那狗屎爸爸
I don't remember shit about my dad.
我不记得他的尖叫
I don't remember him yelling.
我不记得他的微笑
I don't remember him smiling.
老实说 我都不记得他长啥样了
To be honest with you, I don't even remember what the hell he looked like.
我不记得了  他....
I don't remember. He just...
他好像根本就没存在过
He was just never there.
你不会那样的  Brian
You ain't going to be like that, Brian.
我们不能一直逃命 Dom
We can't keep running, Dom.
我们都抽身出来
We got to get out.
我们现在就得抽身出来
We got to get out now.
你说的对
You're right.
这就是我们抽身出来的方法
Here's how we're going to do it.
我们得利用这个
We're going to use this.
还得最后干一票
We're going do one last job.
我们去把Reyes的金库洗劫一空
We're going to take all of Reyes' money.
一分一厘都不放过
Every dime of it,
然后就溜之大吉
and disappear.
永远消失
Forever.
新护照
New passports.
过上再也不用担惊受怕的新生活
New lives with no more looking over our shoulder.
我们要买回我们的自由
And we're just going to buy our freedom.
说的对
That's right.
你清楚我们要面对的是
You realize we're talking about going up against
全里约最有权势的家伙吗?
the most powerful guy in all of Rio?
是的 我们很清楚
Yes, we are.
那么我们就来组个队吧
Then we're going to need a team.
快点在这人才库里查查     我们都可以找谁?
Let's run through the bases real quick. Who do we got?
首先我们要找个伪装者
First we're going to need a chameleon.
可以随时随地变身的家伙
Someone who can blend in anywhere.
还有呢?
What else?
大忽悠
A fast talker.
可以帮我们忽悠出任何困境的家伙
Someone who can bullshit their way out of anything.
我来找
I got that.
那家伙肯定会安很多监控
This guy is going to have a lot of surveillance.
我们还需要一个懂电子的家伙
We're going to need someone who’s good with circuits.
说到这个     Reyes 肯定会设很多障碍
DOM: And with those circuits, Reyes is going to have walls.
我们都找些可以打通这些障碍的家伙
We're going to need guys to punch through those walls.
还有呢?
MIA: What else?
打杂的和武器
Utilities and weapons.
可以随时牺牲的家伙
Someone who ain't afraid to throw down.
随时可以补位的家伙
Someone to back up every position.
对 我们还需要些啥?
BRIAN: Yeah, what else do we need?
最重要的
DOM: Most importantly,
我们还需要两名飞车手
we're going to need two precision drivers.
心理素质极强
Guys that don't crack under pressure.
永远求胜的家伙
Guys that never lose.
你知道我们不缺这个
You know we got that.
哇 绝对不行
Aw, hell, no!
我想他们真的是城中无大将 廖化当先锋 是不?
I see they really scraped the bottom of the barrel, huh?
我想是吧 自从你来了过后
I guess they did, since your ass is here.
你啥时候把车还给Martin Luther King?(黑人领袖)
When are you going to give Martin Luther King his car back?
只要你先把夹克还给Rick James(黑人放克音乐大师)   (两人在互相嘲笑对方老土)
As soon as you give Rick James his jacket back.
咋样 兄弟?    咋样?
What's up, man? What's up?
Hmm.
美腿啊   小宝贝儿
Sexy legs, baby girl.
他们什么时候打开?(暗指张开双腿)
What time do they open?
我一开枪他们就会打开
They open the same time as I pull this trigger.
要我开枪不?(张开双腿)
Want me to open them?
(TEGO SPEAKING SPANISH)
448 C
早就跟你说过这小妞脾气暴
I told you the skinny chick had balls.
看起来她不等我们到齐就开始high了
Looks like she started the party without us.
嘿 这里没人他妈妈的会说西班牙语 兄弟
Hey, anybody can talk shit in Spanish, homie.
那家伙瞎扯啥?
What's this guy saying?
西班牙语或者英语里说:凤姐始终是凤姐 咋整都没用
Ugly is still ugly in Spanish or in English.
(BOTH TAUNTING IN SPANISH)
这些小丑是谁?  马戏团的(谐音电子小丑)
Who are these clowns, man? Circus clowns.
我还以为斗鸡在巴西是违法的
I thought cockfights were illegal in Brazil.
我想你们都相互认识了吧
I see you all have met.
你知道当你叫我来里约的时候
You know when you called me to come to Rio
我还以为是来整点比这更刺激的事儿
I assumed it would be for something more exciting than this.
看这家伙
Look at this guy.
好久不见 我想死你了
Long time. I missed you, man.
我也是
Good to see you.
兄弟 还好吧?
Brother. What's up?
哟   瞧瞧这家伙  这是Tej
Yo, check this out. This is Tej.
东岸最叼的电路仔
Best circuit man on the East Coast.
这是我兄弟 Roman Pearce
And this is my boy, Roman Pearce.
我们是老交情了 我们在少年惩戒所就认识了
We go way back, I met this guy in juvie.
在迈阿密的时候他就跟我一起干过一票
I pulled that job with him in Miami.
久仰 久仰
I've heard about you.
地方不错啊
Nice digs.
是  主要是 Ritz酒店没房了
Yeah, well, the Ritz was sold out.
那么我们来干嘛的 Dom?
So what's this all about, Dom?
对啊 兄弟 你大老远的把我们拖来是图个啥?
Yeah, man, why did you drag us halfway around the world?
因为我们有活干了
Because we got a job.
好吧 我们的目标是Hernan Reyes
All right, so our target's name is Hernan Reyes.
他是这里的最大的毒贩
And he runs the drug scene down here.
他从来没被逮到过是因为他从不留下书面痕迹
He's never been busted because he doesn't leave a paper trail.
没有书面痕迹就意味着没有经过银行
No paper trail means no banks.
不经过银行就意味着他有放现金的场所
And no banks means cash houses.
对  是有十个  确切的讲
That's right. Ten of them, to be exact.
分布在城市各处
Spread throughout the city.
而我们要把这些地方都给抄了
And we're going to hit them all.
全部?
All of them?
全部
All of them.
听起来有够疯狂的
That sounds crazy.
你带我们到一个陌生的城市
You bring us to a whole other country
来抢他们的龙头老大?
so we can rob the dude who runs it?
我还以为是来做生意咧
I thought this was business.
听起来好像有点对我不满哦
Sounds personal to me.
就这样?
Is that what this is?
我拿你们当兄弟   但是义气用事做不成大事
I got love for y'all, but personal ain't good business.
我做不来 兄弟
I can't do this, homie.
我们说的可以1亿美刀哦
So what we're talking about is $100 million.
你说啥?
You say what?
1亿     你瞧 兄弟  有时候我是有点二
Hundred... See, sometimes I be over thinking, man,
我知道我们刚认识   但你 有点 ...
and I know we just met, but you just, kind of, got to...
是的 1亿美刀 然后我们平分
That's right, $100 million, and everything we take,
一切
we split even.
每人大概是1千1百万
TEJ: That's a little over $11 million apiece.
我参加
I am down.
I'm in.
1千1百万
Eleven million.
想想就来劲
Sounds like a whole lot of vaginal activity to me.
你不可能同时抢十个地方啊
You can't pull off 10 heists on the same mark.
没法啊
You just can't.
只要我们拿下第一个
As soon as we hit the first one,
他们肯定会想尽办法保护剩下的
they're going to do everything they can to protect the rest.
没错
Exactly.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
都别动!
Nobody move!
全在这儿了
That's all of it.
你死定了
You a dead man.
你们都死定了!
You're all dead men!
你无处可藏了
You don't have a place to hide.
谁要藏了?
Who's hiding?
你疯啦?
THUG: Are you crazy?
Are you crazy?
你知道那是谁的地盘吗?你知道你偷的是谁的钱吗?
Do you know whose house this is? Whose money are you stealing?
我们可没偷哦
We ain't stealing it.
你可以告诉你老板是谁干的
You tell your boss exactly who did this.
告诉他还没完
Tell him there's more coming.
完工
Voilà.
发动
Turn it over.
八个缸都启动了 一切正常
She's running on all eight. Checks out fine.
继续找
Keep looking.
老大 如果少了什么东西 我们看的到的
Boss, if something was missing, we'd know.
这么经典的车上装这垃圾玩意儿可真不搭啊
It's a goddamn shame putting bullshit like that on a classic.
那氖灯也是
You may as well slap neon lights on it.
他们拿走了芯片
They took the chip.
警用频道上有消息   有人武装抢劫了Leblon的一处寓所
We got a hit on the police scanner. Armed robbery at a house in Leblon.
追查出来屋主是
Address cross-checks against property
Hernan Reyes的一家公司
owned by one of Hernan Reyes' corporations.
好 如果是那几爷子干的
All right, if that's our guys
那不管芯片上都有些啥 都会引领我们去到那寓所
then whatever was on that chip led them directly to that house.
是他们干的 我确定
It's them, for sure.
你怎么知道?
How do you know that?
因为在里约还没有人蠢到敢去抢Reyes
Because no one else in Rio is stupid enough to rob Reyes.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
解释
Explain.
他们侵入了Leblon的寓所
They invaded the Leblon house.
谁?
Who invaded?
火车上那帮人
The men from the train.
他们拿了多少走?
How much did they take?
他们啥都没拿
They didn't take anything.
他们一把火给烧了!
They burned it!
他们烧我的钱钱?
They burned my money?
是的 他们还说这仅仅是开始
Yes. And said there's more coming.
好
Okay...
那接下来
Then this...
我们就这么干
...is what we're going to do.
清场
Clean the houses.
我要把钱都锁起来
I want that money under lock and key...
然后一小时内把钥匙给我拿过来
...within an hour.
明白?
Understand?
明白
Understood.
一号目标在移动 兄弟
Number One is on the move, man.
二号也是
ROME: Two is on the move.
我的也是
I got mine.
我盯五号目标
I got eyes on Five.
我知道你们都认为他们要把钱都运到某处去    但是
I know y'all said they were consolidating the money somewhere, but,
但是你们绝对不会相信这个
y'all ain't going to believe this.
额 工作有点棘手了哦
Well, this job just got a lot harder.
如果他给运到警局去
If he's moving it into a police station
那他可得大出血了
he's got some serious brass in his pocket.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
看来要比我预想的旅途要短点....
Looks like this is going to be a shorter trip than I thought...
我咧个去  我们做不了这个
Hell, yeah, we can't do this.
"做不了"? 你是说  "不该做"吧
"Can't"'? You mean, "shouldn't."
我想没什么区别吧
I think this doesn't change a thing.
我说我们还是照原计划吧
I say we stick to the plan.
你说啥?
You say what?
现在都从"不可能完成的任务"
This just went from Mission: Impossible
变成"疯子任务"了
to Mission： In-freaking-sanity.
随你讲啦
Whatever, man.
我不是害怕  我只是想让你们知道 攻进那地方真的是自杀行为啊
I ain't scared, I'm just letting you all know, going in that building is crazy.
我来说服他
BRIAN: I got this.
劫案几点发生的?
What time was the robbery?
11点左右
Around 11:00.
有了
Here we go.
弄清楚点
Enhance it.
他们都蒙面了
Their faces are covered.
用FRS试试
Run it through FRS.
额 你好 你们这些臭不要脸的
Well, hello, you son of a bitch.
Wilkes! 用这些照片对比一下 Toretto 和 O'Conner的同伙
Wilkes! Run the photos of known associates of Toretto and O'Conner
看看海关那里  他们有没有在最近两周内入境
against customs entries into Brazil in the last two weeks.
查查 航班 火车 船舶  所有可能的交通工具
Check planes, trains, boats, everything short of the goddamn space shuttle.
他们可以更名改姓 但是不能换脸吧
They can change their names but they can't change their faces.
有大行动了
Something big is going down.
那是辆1970的突袭者（车名）
That's a 1970 Charger.
Fusco! 马上在信息库查找
Fusco! Upload these specs into the database.
让电脑连同卫星一起追踪
Have the computer cross-check it with overhead satellites
每15分钟一次 还有它后面的小货车
every 15 minutes, the van behind it, too.
如果这些车上路了 我要第一时间知道
If these vehicles move in the streets of Rio, I want to know about it.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
一切顺利?
Everything okay?
一切顺利
Everything is okay.
这Hobbs是个啥人物?这联邦特工在城里乱窜?
Who is this Hobbs? This Federal Agent running around town?
就一美国土老帽
Some American cowboy.
他可厉害咧
He's handled.
干掉了我们16个手下
He killed sixteen of our men.
好好收拾下他
Handle him better.
瞧...他找了个新手巡警来当助手
Look... He requested a rookie patrol officer as his assistant.
他们构不成威胁
They won't be a problem.
全在这儿了? 是的
It's all here? Yes.
Toretto 和 O'Conner呢? 他们在哪儿?
What about Toretto and O'Conner? Where are they?
还没消息
Nothing yet.
但我已经把我的人都派出去了
But I have all our officers searching.
还不够
Not good enough.
悬赏捉拿他们
Put a price on their heads.
赏金要高的
High enough...
让全城的人都想抓到他们
...to get every pair of eyes in the city searching for them.
警局之花?
The beauty of public offices?
官方记录
Public records.
这就是他藏钱的地方 证物室的保险柜里
This is where he's keeping the money. The vault in the evidence room.
额 啊 大家能看过来下不 这里 就一下下?
Um. Uh, yeah. Can I get everyone's attention, right here, for a second?
我们现在可是要闯警局啊
We're talking about breaking into a police station.
有没有人听说过这些词儿?
Is anyone listening to those words?
有人听说过不? 警察叔叔?
Anybody? Popo?
条子   带枪的  差佬
Five-O. One-time. Pigs.
我们可不待见这些家伙
People we don't like.
你懂得 警局是用来关人的 可不是用来放人的
You know, police stations are designed to keep people in, not out.
这就是我们要隐秘行动的原因
That's why it's a stealth mission.
悄悄的进去 打枪的不要 再悄悄的出来
We'll be in and out before they even know we were there.
恩 我们在那儿得弄个眼线
Well, we'll need to get eyes in there.
至少得知道保险柜是什么牌子和型号的
At least to find out the make and model of that vault.
那么保险柜.....
So the vault and then, so...
太疯狂了啊
it's crazy.
那谁来干这差事?
Who's supposed to do all this?
你啥意思?
What do you mean?
为啥挑我?
Why me?
因为你丫就一大忽悠
Because you got the biggest mouth.
这倒不假
That's for damn sure.
Ooh.
你好啊 甜妞儿
Hello, beautiful.
瞧瞧这些小酒窝  靓啊 靓啊
Look at those dimples. Sexy, sexy.
爱死你的眼镜了  你哪儿买的?
Love those glasses. Where did you get them from?
那些跟Gucci的框架很像是不?
Are those like Gucci frames or something?
不懂英语?
No English?
不 不 不 去你丫的
No, no, no. Damn.
你好 警官?
How are you, sir?
特别干探 O'Conner  美国联邦调查局的
Special Agent O'Conner. US Federal Bureau of Investigation.
上面说是白人啊
It says Caucasian.
晒的 懂不 晒得?
That's a tan. You know, a tan?
瞧 我负责这案子 我来这儿放点相关的证据
Look, I'm working this case and I got some evidence here to be held.
但是我得先去你们的证物房看看
But I need to get in and check your storage facility first.
不行
Nope.
瞧 我知道那你很敬业 我很敬佩你 说真的
Look, I know you're a true professional, and I respect you, I promise.
但是 好像你也有在健身哦
You know, it looks like you work out a little bit, too.
你推举的重量多少  350磅?
What do you bench, about 350?
啊 晕
Ah, Shit.
瞧 我只想做好我的本职工作
Look, I'm just trying to do my job, man.
我老大派我来确保一切都万无一失
My boss sent me here to just make sure that everything was safe.
绝对安全
It will be safe.
就让我进去瞧一瞧就好了
Let me just come in and take a quick peek.
不行
Nope.
好了 朋友 帮兄弟一把 行不?
Come on, man. Hook a brother up, please?
不行 况且你也不是我兄弟
Nope. And you're not my brother.
同父异母?
Brother from another mother?
听着! 只有在得到证物处的授权才可以进入证物房
Look! No one enters the facility but authorized evidence personnel.
所以别在这儿瞎掰了
Now stop wasting my time.
我要打电话给大使馆
I'm going to call the embassy.
别 别 别! 别这样
No,no,no! No, we're good.
没必要打电话个 为啥? 我们这里没出问题啊
We don't need to call them. For what? We're good.
给 我把盒子放这儿  我们没事了
Here, I got the box. We're all good.
我答应你  谢谢你
I promise you. Thank you so much for your time.
向上帝发誓 如果你是在我这边的话
Swear to God, if you were on the other side of that glass
我一定把你丫脸摁到上面去   翻译给他听
I'd bust your damn face in. Now translate that.
搞定 瞧 我想我干特工这行比你干的好
It's done. See, I think I make a better special agent than you ever did.
恩 这取决于你如何定义"特"字
Well, that depends on how you define "special."
快点 瞧瞧 我们都能看到些啥
TEJ: Come on, now. Let's see what we got.
不搞笑
Not funny.
好吧 快点
All right, come on.
兄弟 你咋还是个黄师傅呢?
Dawg, you still can't drive.
现在 我终于明白你为什么老出车祸了
Now, I see why you're always getting into accidents.
你丫就连遥控玩具车都不会开
You can't even drive a damn remote control car.
你丫闭嘴
I'm going to need you to shut up right now.
我才不闭嘴   闭嘴
I'm not going to shut up. Shut up.
用安全带把丫给绑起来
Strap him in his safety belt, man.
给我那遥控器 兄弟 走左边
Give me the remote, dawg. Go left.
左边看起来好像有什么东西  是啥?
It looks like something right over there to the left. What is that?
是啥?
BRIAN: What is that?
中!
Bingo.
是啥      六加六?(指门锁上的钢柱门闩)
What is that, six-by-six?
八加十二
Eight-by-twelve.
七加十二
Seven-by-twelve.
配有18英寸厚 的
Fitted with 18-inch-thick steel reinforced walls
黄铜绝缘内芯壁
with a insulated copper core to protect against thermal lance.
三级电子锁  配有Griffin牌的双重制动栓
A Class-3 electronic lock with a surefire Griffin retumbler
和生物掌纹扫描器
and a biometric palm scanner.
一大堆高科技安保设备啊
Ten tons of top-of-the-line security.
有必要告诉我你对这些很了解不?
Do I want to know how you know all that?
我的过去你是不了解滴 O'Conner
I had a life before you knew me, O'Conner.
别跟我抬杠了  好不?
Let's just leave it at that, all right?
不管怎么说 她都是一尤物啊
She is a beauty, though, man.
"尤物" 是指 "很好吧"
A "beauty" as in "good"?
"尤物"的意思就是说她很难得手的
"Beauty" as in, she's going to start off playing hard to get.
无论我怎样的爱抚她  无论我如何的深爱她
Then, no matter how much I caress her, no matter how much I love her,
最终 她还是不会上我的床(指打不开)
in the end, she still ain't going to give up that ass.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
一致认为你拍错了马屁
Two to one says you blow the wrong pipe.
哟 为什么你总跟我抬杠呢?
Yo, why you got to be so negative all the time, man?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
我才没有咧
I ain't negative.
我只是很积极的认为你肯定会搞砸的
I'm just positive you're going to mess it up.
我很负责的告诉你 你有问题
I'm telling you, man, you got issues.
下次如果还没有电梯 我就不来了
Next time if there's no elevator, I'm not coming.
深呼吸 放轻松
You need to learn to relax, loco.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
你得快点 我们还有不到一分钟的时间
You better hurry up, we got less than a minute.
干嘛每次都把时间掐的那么紧?
Why do you always set the timer so short?
(RICO SPEAKING SPANISH)
我希望你知道我们这是去哪儿
I hope you know where you're going.
我知道  放松 伙计
I got this. Relax, man.
放松
Relax.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
警察局
...a police station.
放松
Relax.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
炸药放太多了! 再一次的!
You used too much explosive! Again.
太多  太少
Too much, too little...
傻傻分不清楚
it's all the same.
你在监狱图书馆里就学到些狗屎佛经是吧?
That's some Buddha shit you learned from a book in the prison library, isn't it?
你在那墙上整的事儿
And what you're doing there on the wall...
也是从同一本书里学来的 是吧?
You got that from the same book, huh?
伙计  你又来抬杠了
You're so negative, bro.
给点光成不?
Can I have some light?
成功了  我们成功了
MIA: Got it. We got it!
是啊   我们侵入了他们的四部摄像头
BRIAN: Yeah, we're looking at four cameras.
哟 都是些高科技啊
Yo, that's some high-end shit, too.
Marker 光学镜片
Marker optics.
百度视角
Hundred-degree field-of-view.
十秒循环震动
Ten seconds oscillation.
对    盲区很小啊     兄弟
Yeah, that's a narrow window, man.
我们能不能悄悄进去在镜头前换张图片?
Can't we just tap in and replace the image?
不行 它是数字同步的
No, it's hooked into a digital sync.
他们会发现我们已经进入系统的
They would know we were in the system.
我们唯一能做的只有窥探
The best we can do is peek.
我们得找些马力强劲的车来做事了
We're going to need some real fast cars to get through this.
并不仅仅是跑得快
Not just fast.
那里有右急转弯 还有U型弯
You got a hard right and a hairpin.
我们得找些灵巧的车才行
We're going to need something agile.
你们先做个线路模拟
You guys mock up a track.
O'Conner.
我们去找车
Let's go get some cars.
不错啊
Nice.
还是回家好啊
Home sweet home.
那辆如何
BRIAN: Or that.
那辆如何?  全马达 无需调试
How about that? All motor, no tuning issues.
我一直都梦想拥有一部
I always wanted one of those.
它可保持着Avenida 大街三年的赛车记录
Held the record on the Avenida three years running.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
兄弟
Damn, bro...
你胆子可真够大的  敢到这儿来撒野  Toretto
You got a lot of balls to bring your problems here, Toretto.
更别提还带了个警察
Not to mention a cop.
是 我们可以低调点
Yeah, we can keep that on the low.
江湖传言 有很多人都在找你俩
Word on the street is a lot of people are looking for you two.
什么?
What?
你不会以为我们没认出你俩吧?
You didn't think we'd recognize you?
没有吧 我们还是觉得你们挺靠得住的
No, we're kind of counting on it.
那辆小车车可能能在这里称霸
That little coupe may run the streets around here,
但那辆怪物车可是从未被超越过
but that monster has never seen a set of tail lights.
那敢情好  她马上就要超越了
Even Well, she's about to.
(DIOGO SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Dominic Toretto的车在我的车库里
Dominic Toretto's ride in my garage.
那..将是个不错的战利品
Now that... will be a nice trophy.
出发吧  传说中的哥
Let's go, legend.
以车赌车
Car for car.
以车赌车?
Car for car?
想要 就凭本事来拿
DIOGO: You want it, come and get it.
看看他们都有什么本事
Let's see what they got.
真的?
Really?
你从谁哪儿抢来的?蓝爸爸?(蓝精灵)
Where did you get that from? Papa Smurf?
好吧 O'Conner   演场好戏给我看
Okay, O'Conner, give it your best shot.
怎么样?
How was that one?
镜头拍到你了
Camera caught you.
什么? 对 依然拍到你了
What? Yeah, it still caught you.
兄弟 我吃奶的劲都使完了
Man, I was milking the hell out of that thing, too.
我们得弄辆更快的车
We're going to need a faster car.
我要发财 快点 兄弟
I want my money. Come on, man.
Yeah!
来吧! 瞧着
Let's get it! Watch this.
这就是你丫不会开车的原因
That's exactly why your ass ain't been driving.
我想我恋爱了
I think I'm in love.
干得不错
That was real solid work.
我认为3号镜头还是拍得到你
I think Camera 3 still caught you, though.
再来一次
Let's do it again.
这是你订购的猪猪存钱罐
TEGO: That's the piggy bank you ordered.
你玩儿我  咋地
You're kidding me. Yep.
你丫到底在哪儿拿到这玩意儿的?
Where in the hell did y'all get one of these?
恩 哥们儿以前的生活你是不了解滴
Well, we had a life before you met us.
好吧 我来弄锁的电子制动栓
All right, I'll get to work on the electronic tumbler
但是还有个问题
but there's still another problem.
掌纹扫描
Palm scanner.
没有Reyes的掌纹
And without Reyes' handprint,
Houdini(著名逃脱魔术大师)也打不开这娘们
Houdini himself couldn't open this bitch.
你怎么知道是要用Reyes的掌纹?
How do you know it's Reyes' handprint?
你丫保险柜了放了1亿美刀
You got $100 million in a safe.
你会用其他人的掌纹来开锁吗?
You going to put somebody else's handprint on it?
这玩意儿能生吃了你
That shit is eating you alive.
你来试试
You check that.
哟 试试就试试   你丫闭嘴!
Yo, check that. Shut up!
我们怎么才能得到Reye的掌纹?
How are we supposed to get Reyes' handprint?
Han
Han.
看你的了
You're up.
瞧好吧  小菜一碟
Sure. Nothing like the easy stuff.
我们走吧 我来开车
Let's go. I'll drive.
-6个保镖  -7个
I make six bodyguards. Seven.
你不会觉得那个挎着腰包的人是个旅客吧?
You think that guy with a fanny pack is a tourist?
你在军队呆了多久?
So, how long were you in the army?
那天你拿的那把枪是杰里科941
That gun you pulled the other day was a Jericho 941.
拇指放扳机旁?
Thumb-racking the slide?
绝对是摩萨德的造型(以色列特工)
That was straight-up Mossad.
我在军队呆的时间
I got out of the military
和你的烟龄差不多
probably the same time you quit smoking.
你吃这么多薯条
The amount of chips you eat,
让自己的嘴巴和手不闲着
the way you always have to keep your hands and mouth busy,
我可以总结出 你一天抽两包
you were a two-pack-a-day man for sure.
还不用滤嘴
Unfiltered.
这任务真艰巨
Well, this is a bust.
我们不可能在这拿到那家伙的掌纹
We're not going to be able to get his fingerprints out here.
我们得再做些调查 再召集几个人过来
We need to do some more recon, call in a couple of extra guys.
或者
Or
老娘出马   爷们靠边
you don't send a man to do a woman's job.
我们一定能搞定它 我保证
We're going to figure this out, I promise you.
什么情况?
What's up?
这事绝对不会只是条丁字裤那么简单
I thought you were more of a thong, man.
我们拿到掌纹了
We got the print.
哪呢?
Where?
好吧 这可真火爆
Okay, that's crazy.
那 他是拍了你屁股一下 还是掐了一下 还是抓住了就没松手呢
So, did he just slap that ass or did he grab and hold on to it?
这个可帮了大忙了
Hey, this will work.
哥被震惊了
I'm impressed.
-能提取吧 ? -能的
Got it? Got it.
你还是没回答哥的问题呢
But you still didn't answer the question.
哦 不 哥几个 ! 快过来我们有麻烦了
Oh, no. Guys, guys! Guys, we have a problem.
我们被发现了
The whole team just got burnt.
现在外头正通缉我们呢
Now we're all wanted.
怎么会这样?
How did this happen?
美国外交安全部已授权逮捕令于
US Diplomatic Security Service issued the warrants.
L. Hobbs探员
Agent L. Hobbs.
等下
Hold on one second.
嘿 Dom
Hey, Dom.
这是你在贫民窟见到的那家伙吗?
Is that the guy you saw in the favela?
是他
Yeah.
Hobbs是DDS精英小组的头头
Hobbs is the leader of the elite task force for the DSS.
那他很厉害吧
So he's good.
如果FBI想通缉谁 他们就会让Hobbs去做
When the FBI wants to find somebody, that's who they call.
因为他从未失手
Because he never misses his mark.
这哥们是一传说
This guy is Old Testament.
这家伙的作风十分硬派
Blood, bullets, wrath of God. That's his style.
现在他在追捕我们是吗?
And right now he's hunting us?
Dom 我们得提前行动
Dom, we got to move up our timeline.
现在?
Yeah, but how?
没有Wyatt Earp的帮忙 这事对我们来说本来就有点难搞
This thing's already been difficult without Wyatt Earp on our asses.
我们得给自己留下后路
If anything, we need more room to breathe.
Roman说得对
Roman's right.
我们都快喘不过气来了
Think we need to get some fresh air.
目标锁定  70'突击者
We've got a hit.'70s Charger.
行动
Let's get a move on!
东行向Avenida
Eastbound on Avenida Atlantica.
快快快
Move, move, move, move!
目标距我们一街区的位置停下
It stopped about a block ahead.
停车 我们走过去
Park it. We're going on foot.
嘿   Toretto
Hey, Toretto.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
被捕?
Arrest?
我可不这么认为
I don't feel like I'm under arrest.
你说呢   Brian?
How about you, Brian?
一点也不觉得
No, not a bit.
一丁点都不觉得
Not even a little bit.
给你一分钟时间好好想想
Just give it a minute. it'll sink in.
我没有杀那些人 是Reyes干的
BRIAN: We didn't kill those feds. That was Reyes.
我不在乎这个
HOBBS: I don't give a shit.
我就是来这将你们缉拿归案的
I'm just here to bring in two assholes whose names hit my desk.
哟  说的你像个救世主似的
Yeah, that sounds like a real hero.
有点意思
That's funny.
这话来自一个宣过誓要当警察  可是转身之后就违背誓言的人
From a guy who took the oath  of a cop, then went against everything it stood for.
或者你想成为个硬汉
Or some wanna be tough guy prick
就是那种用扳手把人打得半死不活的硬汉
who beat a man half to death with a socket wrench.
的确是硬汉
Yeah, real tough.
转过去把手放在背后
You turn around and put your hands behind your back.
如果我不这么做呢
I don't think so.
你错在总以为自己会有第二选择 小朋友
Your mistake is thinking you got a goddamn choice, boy.
那你错在哪呢?
And your mistake?
你错在以为你这是在美国
Thinking you're in America.
这可不是你的主场
You're a long way from home.
这里是巴西
This is Brazil.
走吧 头儿 改天再找他算账
Come on, boss. Another day.
走吧  头儿   他们太强势了
Come on, H, it's a lot of heat.
Toretto   后会有期
I'll see you soon, Toretto.
我很期待 警察先生
I look forward to it, cop.
说
Yep.
跟踪器就位
Tracker's on.
收到
Got them.
我不明白 来这干嘛?
I don't understand. Why come here?
为了20刀的银饰冒这样的险 值吗?
Why risk it all for $20 worth of silver?
值
Because it's worth it.
还是快逃吧
You should run,you know.
Hobbs迟早会找到你的
Hobbs will find you.
你该离开的  留下来干什么?
You have every reason to leave. Why stay?
那你呢?
Why do you?
我丈夫是个尽忠职守的警察
My husband was a good police officer.
一个真诚的人
An honest man.
我们都在这长大
We both grew up here.
2年前他在大街上被谋杀
Two years ago he was murdered in the street
就在我们家门前的那条街
right outside our door.
Reyes现在是这贫民窟的主人   他施舍这里的人民
Reyes owns this favela now. He gives things to people.
但也剥削了他们
But everything has a price.
这的人民需要新的生活
The people here need a new start.
自由的生活
They need to be free.
在火车上 你没有杀死那些人
You didn't kill those men in the train,
不是吗?
did you?
为什么你现在才开始相信我说的每一句话了 ?
Now, why would you believe anything I would tell you?
喂!
Hey!
她对你来说很特别是吧?
Was she so special to you?
我从未期待过有人会理解她对我的重要
I never thought anyone could understand now much.
但是你知道
But you do.
是啊!
Yeah!
接近了   可还是不够好
Close, but not enough.
Dom 这盲区有点小
Dom, the window is too small, man.
用隐形车是躲过摄像头的唯一方法
Only way we're going to beat the cameras is with invisible cars.
我知道去哪能搞到
And I know just where to get them.
走吧   哥几个
Let's take a ride, boys.
小心点
Don't hurt yourself.
我已经好久没开过警车了
It's been a while since I've been behind the wheel of one of these.
我头次坐前排啊....
First time I've ever been in the front seat.
Rome 你磨蹭啥?
Rome, what took you so long?
我还以为你要带着闪圈圈登场咧
I thought for sure you'd be showing up with some chrome spinners or something.
一点都不好笑
Real funny.
我赌10万美刀  哥四分之一英里后就把你们都甩掉
I got $100,000 that says I can take you all in the next quarter-mile.
是啊  你个穷屁股有个屁钱啊
Yeah, your broke ass has got a hundred grand.
如果这个事成了 我就有了
If we pull off this job,I will.
过了前面两个红绿灯
The next two lights.
10万刀
Hundred thousand.
这事要是没成 我们几个也就挂了
We don't pull this job off, we're probably dead anyway.
把赌注变成100万刀
Let's make it a million.
我喜欢 来吧  100W刀的四分之一英里加速赛
I like that. All right, a million-dollar quarter-mile.
太棒了
All right, then.
死而无憾了 豁出去了
You only live once. Let's do it.
Dom 说句话啊?
What do you say, Dom?
是赛车还是要鸡婆?
We talking or we racing?
这回可不能作弊了
Just don't cheat this time.
往事不要再提
Got to let that go.
爽!
Yeah!
Roman 又来了
Typical, Roman.
我要拿到那笔钱 我胃口很大的
I'm going to get this money. I'm hungry.
哥几个别让着我啊
Don't make it too easy for me, boys.
不!
No!
这回可不能让你赢 Dom
Not this time, Dom.
我就让你输得心甘情愿 Brian
You got to want it, Brian.
耶! 我赢了!  我赢了!
Yeah! Owned you! Owned you!
-O'Conner 干得不错  -谢了   Dom
Good race, O'Conner. Thanks, Dom.
等了好久终于等到今天  梦了好久终于把梦实现
Do you know how long I've been waiting for that shit?
我都说了他没看出来
I told you he didn't see it.
你那兄弟?
Your man right there?
还没过终点  就松开油门了
He let off the throttle at the line.
他没想赢     他让你的
You didn't do nothing.He let you win.
扯淡
Bullshit.
Vince 你干啥呢? 安静点!  他们在跟踪你
Vince, what are you doing? Quiet! They've been tracking you.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
我就知道她在这!
I know she's here!
快点找到她!
Find her!
快!快!快!
Go!Go!Go!
没事的 等等!
It's okay. Wait!
Reyes的手下正在市场里找我
Reyes' guys were waiting for me at the market.
Vince救了我
Vince saved my life.
饿没?
DOM: You hungry?
-饿了 -很好
Yeah, sure. -Good.
因为你在做餐前的感恩祈祷
Because you're saying grace.
谢了 Vince
Thanks, Vince.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
哟 你都给烤焦了!
Yo, you burned it!
我这是跟我妈学的 放心吧
Yo, this is how my momma does it. Relax.
是啊 可是你老妈是最差的厨师
Yeah, but your mom is the worst cook in the world.
喂 别说我妈妈的不是
Yo, don't you be talking about my momma.
来吧 宝贝们 没有比这更好的日子了
Yeah, come on, baby. Who's good living?
敬你 兄弟 干杯
To you, bro.Cheers, cheers, cheers.
在巴西的日子可真好
ROME: So, we in Brazil.it's the good life.
是啊
Yeah.
是啊 你1000w刀马上就入手了
So, you got a little more than $10 or $11 million coming.
打算那这些钱干点什么?
What you going to do with your money?
-我 -是啊
Me? Yeah.
事实上 哥们 我想过回家后要开一个汽车修理厂
Actually, man, I been thinking about opening up a garage back home.
人们把车子放在我那修 然后我慢慢宰他们
Place where people can bring their cars and not get completely ripped off.
你懂我的意思吗?
You know what I mean?
-真的这么想? - 恩
-Really? -Yeah.
也就是说你想好好工作?
So, your dream is to start a day job?
太二了 就像...
That's stupid. Like, why would...
不 一点也不二 我就是喜欢这么做
No, it's not stupid at all. I love what I do.
这对我来说毫无意义
That don't make no sense to me.
我很清楚我要拿这些钱干什么
I know what I'm going to do with my money.
给我兄弟买点烹饪教程
Buying some cooking lessons for my man.
看见没?  看见没?
See? See?
你就不能不抬杠吗?
There you go with that negativity, man.
你知道我的 不差钱
You know me.Money ain't a goddamn thing.
学习怎么烹饪不仅仅是钱能搞定的
It's going to take a little more than money to learn how to cook.
太吓人了
That's horrible.
我可听说那边的动物避难所招厨师啊
But I heard they was looking for a chef down at this animal shelter.
你不是想...
You might want to...
我认识那经理
I know the manager.
嘿  Dom
Hey, Dom.
听着
Listen.
我知道你想明天就动手
I know that you're all set for this job tomorrow,
但如果你还需要人手的话 我可以....
but if you need an extra man, I could...
算你一份
You're in.
我家大门一直为你敞开
There's always room for family.
谢了
Thank you.
去吃点东西吧
Get something to eat.
Yeah.
你能相信Mia把这个称为诅咒吗?
Can you believe Mia calls this a curse?
她可能没错
She might be right.
你真的很喜欢摆弄这些 是吗?
You really like doing that stuff, huh?
人在江湖  身不由己
When your life is on the line that's when you learn about yourself.
那倒不假
That's a fair deal.
离我们人生中最光辉的时刻还有不到24小时
We're less than 24 hours from the biggest celebration of our life.
你们都得再加点油  这玩意儿可带劲哦
Y'all need a refill. This is serious stuff.
不 我就不喝了 干杯  宝贝儿
No, I'm good. Cheers, baby.
不喝了  谢了
I'm good. No, thank you.
不 她不能喝
No, she can't.
你啥意思? 她不能喝
What do you mean? She can't.
她为啥不能喝? 神马...
What do you mean she can't? What is...
你说真的?
Are you serious right now?
这就是你在刚才赛车的时候让他的原因?
Is that the reason you let him beat you in the quarter-mile?
那是送你家小宝贝的礼物   不 不能混为一谈
That was a baby gift. No, that's messed up.
不 你不能这样混为一谈
No, you're not taking that from me.
等等 稍等一下
Wait, wait, hold on a second.
那么 他到底是拍了你的屁股 还是抓了你的屁股  还是放在上面就没拿开过?
So, did he just smack the ass or did he grab and hold on to it?
到底是哪一个?
Which One was it?
恭喜啊  谢谢
Congratulations. Thank you.
你怎么能瞒着不说呢?
ROME: How can you keep this a secret?
有点扯 是吧?  是你的孩子啊
Crazy, huh? ROME: It's your boy.
像这种好事你怎么能瞒着我呢?
ROME: Why would you keep something like that away from me?
新生儿礼物 是吧?
Baby gift, huh?
我完全不知道他们在说什么?
I have no idea what they're talking about. Oh?
抽出法(体外射精)咋就不管用了咧?
TEJ: What happened to the pull-out method, man?
祝酒词
Toast
金钱有进有出   我们都有清楚
Money will come and go. We know that.
生命中最重要的是   我们周围的朋友
But the most important thing in life will always be the people in this room.
此地
Right here.
此时的朋友
Right now.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(ALL REPLYING IN ITALIAN)
我准备好了
I'm all set.
哟 Santos  车备好了吗?
HAN: Yo, Santos. Van good?
时刻准备着 兄弟
You know we're always good, bro.
Hobbs 在城市的另外一头
Hobbs is on the other side of the city.
现在的时机再好不过了
We're not going to get a better window.
好吧 兄弟们  好戏开场了!
Okay, guys, it's show time!
一组到位  出发
First team in position, let's go.
来吧 动手吧
TEGO: Come on, let's do this.
嘿 Dom
Hey, Dom.
我会看好Mia的
I got eyes on Mia.
莫斯科 巴里  果阿  香港
Moscow, Bali, Goa, Hong Kong.
他们都有什么共同之处?
And what do they all have in common?
没有引渡法
No extradition.
离成功还有一小时
We're one hour away from the rest of our lives.
Yeah.
警察!
Cops!
快 出发
Come on. Go.
你犯下了大错
You just made a big mistake.
找到你放的跟踪器花了我点时间
Took me a while to find that tracking chip.
不过要找到接收器可就容易的多了
But not as long to flip the receiver.
你玩完了    Toretto
You're going down, Toretto.
我就在这儿 来抓我啊
I'm right here.
Dom! 退后  别插手
Dom! Stand back. I got this.
分开! Dom!  求你了 停手!
Pull off! Dom! Please, stop!
Dom!
讲
Yeah.
我们在路上
We're coming in now.
等我们降落后 让州警在机场接我们
Have the marshals meet us at the airport when we land.
有埋伏!
Ambush!
Wilkes  压制射击   把他们干掉
Wilkes, suppression fire. Shut them down.
飘忽走位 掩护我
Stagger-step. Cover me.
看好他们!
Watch them!
松开我们!
Cut us loose!
快啊! 松开我们!
Come on! Cut us loose!
都没事吧? 对 开车 快开车!
We're good? Yeah, let's go, let's go!
嘿 Dom
VINCE: Hey, Dom.
你该见见我儿子
You've got to meet my son.
Nico.
有机会的
I will.
他是个好孩子
He's a good kid.
我们给他取了你的名字
You know, we named him after you.
"Dominic."
我答应你 Vince
You've got my word, Vince.
你一直都是我兄弟
You were always my brother.
我会好好照顾Nico的
I got eyes on Nico now.
我们得继续行动 我们耗不起了
We need to move. We don't have that much time.
我找到飞机送我们出去了
I got us a flight out.
五个小时了后 我们就可以消失在里约
We can leave Rio in the rearview in the next five hours.
不是逃命
Not to run away.
而是完成任务
To finish the job.
你疯了嘛 Dom?  我们玩不起了
Are you crazy, Dom? We can't.
完全就是自杀行为
ROME: It's a suicide mission.
你兄弟都为此而挂了
That's your man over there on the table.
你的计划完蛋了!
The plan is busted!
胡扯 小子  Reyes 知道我们要来!
This is bullshit, man. Reyes knows we're coming!
他说的对
TEJ: He's right.
他们已经在警局里严加戒备了
They tripled the detail at the police station.
那里将会是枪林弹雨
TEJ: it's going to be a wall of gunfire.
Reyes逃不掉的
Reyes doesn't get away with this.
这是个坑 兄弟
It's a trap, man.
你是知道的
You know that.
Dom 听听劝吧
Dom, listen to them.
逃吧 在还不是太迟的时候  逃离里约吧
Run, before it's too late. Leave Rio.
你就能自由了
You can be free.
逃离带不来自由
Running ain't freedom.
你很清楚
You should know that.
没人能左右你们的决定
You know you're all free to make your own choices.
我加入
HOBBS: I'm in.
我会跟你并肩作战
I'll ride with you, Toretto.
至少我们得把那狗杂种给干掉
At least until we kill that son of a bitch.
那计划呢 Dom?
BRIAN: So what's the plan, Dom?
偷偷摸摸已经不行了
We can't just go sneaking around anymore.
我们不偷偷摸摸
We don't sneak.
我们只要他的钱
The only thing he cares about is his money.
抢钱
We pull that,
干他
we pull him.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
看见没?
See?
我把我手下的所有警察都叫来了
I called in every cop on our payroll.
我们罩这儿
We're covered.
每个入口都荷枪实弹的守着
We've got every entrance covered with weapons teams.
上帝来了也没法
God Himself couldn't get at your money if He wanted to.
我才不鸟上帝
God isn't my worry.
你准备好了、
You ready?
好了
I'm ready.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
咋啦?
What's happening?
他们在搬保险库!
They're taking the vault!
什么? 保险库啊!
What? The vault!
跟我来! 动作快!
Follow me! Quickly!
让我过去!
Let me through!
别动!
Don't move!
趴下
Stay down.
指令 Mia!
Call it out, Mia!
你有两条街区的直行道
You've got a straight shot for two blocks.
往右  收到
Go right. Got it.
恩 计划起作用了
Well, the plan is working.
全里约的坏警察都在追你们  你们得快点啊
You guys have every corrupt cop in Rio on your tail. You have to move fast.
最佳路线是什么?
What's the best route?
好 再直行半英里 到达Rua Fonseca
Okay, keep going straight another half-mile onto Rua Fonseca,
然后转左
and then go left.
行不通啊
That ain't going to work.
拦车钉  Dom  前面有拦车钉!
Spikes ahead, Dom. We got spikes!
我们往右!
We're going right!
弯太急了 我们转不过去
No, it's too tight, we're not going to fit.
没得选了 动手!
We've got no choice. Now!
妈的!
Shit!
你妈妈的!
Holy shit!
小伙子们 我一直在听你们瞎扯 你们不会是抢了家银行吧?
Guys, I am hearing all this chatter. Did you just take out a bank?
迎面来了两辆车!
Two inbound!
好 在那你左前方有一小巷子
All right, there's an alley coming up on your left.
好  明白
Yeah, I got it.
你个小杂种!
You little bastard!
干的漂亮 Dom  右转 在这儿 右转
All right, good job, Dom. Right-hander, right here, right-hander.
伙计们  在南面有一大群警察向你们扑来了
Guys, there's a big group coming at you from the south.
快想想办法!
You have to do something now!
嘿  分开
Hey, go wide.
漂亮!
Yeah!
左方安全
You're all clear on the left.
下午好啊 警官!
Good afternoon, officer!
驾照 行车证!
License and registration, please!
瞧! 这可是大男孩的游戏!
Yes! This is big-boy stuff!
右方安全
We're clear on the right.
哦 兄弟
Oh, man.
谢了 伙计们
Thanks, guys.
随时效劳
Any time.
另一边见
I'll see you on the other side.
你们有10秒钟的空挡
You guys just carved out a 10-second window.
好好利用!
Make it count!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Zizi  跟紧他们
Zizi, stay on them.
在桥上他们就没法超车了
They can't outrun us on the bridge.
妈妈的
Shit.
他们无路可逃了
They have no way out.
不!
No!
他们人太多了
There's too many of them.
嘿 他们人太多了 我们甩不掉他们
Hey, there's too many of them. We're not going to make it.
你说对了 我们没法
You're right, we aren't.
但是你可以
You are.
你在说些啥?
What are you talking about?
松掉保险柜  你自己逃
Just let the vault go. Get out of there.
你是要做父亲的人了 Brian
You're a father now, Brian.
不  我不会抛弃你的    继续按计划进行
No, I'm not leaving you. Now you stick with the plan!
我一直都这么计划的
It was always the plan.
照顾好Mia
Take care of Mia.
Dom  听我说 好吗?
Dom, you listen to me now. Okay?
你现在就松开
You cut loose right now.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
嘿 他在干嘛?
Hey, what is he doing?
我们快抓到他了!
We've got him!
封锁大桥!
Close down the bridge!
想想办法  蠢货!
Do something, asshole!
干掉他 你妈妈的!
Kill him, dammit!
干掉他!
Kill him now!
我想我告诉过你继续的
I thought I told you to go on.
是啊  但我也得做个决定
Yeah, I had to make a call.
救我
Help me.
这是为我的组员  你个狗娘养的
That's for my team, you son of a bitch.
这是一团糟啊
It's a hell of a mess.
是啊 确实
Yeah, it is.
你知道我不能放你俩走
You know I can't let you two go.
我不能这样就放了你们
I ain't made that way.
但是我的理解是  你们还有24个小时的时间(逃命)
The way I see it, you've earned yourselves 24 hours.
但是钱得留下
The money stays, though.
如果我是你们  我会好好的利用这时间
If I were you, I'd use the time.
放下屠刀  立地成佛
Make peace with whatever demons you got left.
因为明天开始
Because come tomorrow,
我又会追捕你们
I will find you.
Toretto!
后会有期
I'll see you soon.
后会无期
No, you won't.
谢谢 伙计们
Thanks, guys.
另一头见
I'll see you on the other side.
你们有10秒钟的空挡
You guys just carved out a 10 second window.
好好利用!
Make it count!
加油吧 宝贝儿
Come on, baby.
别耍小性子
Don't be mean.
来吧
Come on.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
"给Rosa和Nico 回见  --Dom蜀黍"
”For Rosa and Nico. See you soon, -Uncle Dom”
摩洛哥
MONACO
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
你确定?
You sure about this?
你懂得
You know I am.
你没必要这样做
You don't need to do this.
让我自己来
Just leave me alone.
兄弟  我可不是跟你抬杠    赌场这地方
Bro, I'm not trying to be negative, but casinos
就是专门用来赢你我这样的人的钱的
are the kinds of places designed to take money from guys like you and me.
等我赢了 我要给你买够你吃一辈子的抗抑郁药
When I win here I'm buying you a lifetime supply of antidepressants.
你也不能把1000万都押红上面啊!
You don't put ten million on red!
够啦
Enough already.
你全押黑上
You put it on black.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
停止下注
No more bets.
这边 宝贝儿
Right this way, my dear.
你就呆这儿  我一会儿就回来
You stay right here, I'll be right back.
那么 这就是你的梦想 ?
So, this is your dream, huh?
这就是我的农妇  山泉 有点田  兄弟!
It's enough for me, man.
我想那就是你的梦想吧
I take it that's your dream.
当然 还好吧 兄弟? 还好吧?
Absolutely. What up, boy? What's going on?
一切都好? 当然 当然
You good?  Yes, yes.
你知道最疯的是啥不?
You know what's crazy?
全世界只有四部这样的车
There's only four of those cars in the whole world.
而我拥有Western Hemisphere唯一的一辆
Yeah, I got the only one in the Western Hemisphere.
我给Abu Dhabi的一个酋长开出了一个他无法拒绝的价
I made a sheikh in Abu Dhabi an offer he could not refuse.
嗯  你带来的小妞也不错啊
Huh. That's a nice lady you got there, too.
当然  有事吗?
Absolutely. What's happening?
我们得走了  开工了
We got to go, man. Let's do this.
好吧 我来开车
Okay, I'll drive.
那车? 不是吧  兄弟  没门
In that? Come on, man, no way.
不 不  不是这个
No, no. Not in this.
是那部车
In that.
你没开玩笑吧?
Are you serious right now?
伙计  真的太疯了!
Man, this is crazy!
是啊 我猜在Western Hemisphere应该有两辆这样的车了 是不?
Yes, I guess that means there are two in the Western Hemisphere, huh?
你丫现在还有啥好说的?
What's your smart ass got to say now?
你知道不? 咱哥俩都可以穿一条裤衩了
You know what? We can always shine together, baby.
快去换衣服 我们该干活了!
Get dressed, man, we got things to do!
我们去哪儿?
So, where to now?
不知道
I don't know.
从未去过马德里
Never been to Madrid.
我还以为你要去东京
I thought you wanted to go to Tokyo.
会去的
We'll get there.
一定会去的
Eventually.
大惊喜啊!
BRIAN: Nice surprise.
有点疯 是吧?
Crazy, right?
这是我妹最幸福的时刻
This is the happiest I've ever seen my sister.
因为我们自由了
It's because we're free.
你知道吗  我想再赛一次
You know, I want another shot.
是吗?
Yeah?
对
Yeah.
不要赌注   不要其他人参与
No wagers, nobody else.
就你和我   一劳永逸
Just you and me, once and for all.
你确定你输得起?
You sure you can handle the disappointment?
你呢?
Are you?
好吧   O'Conner
All right, O'Conner.
让我瞧瞧你都有些啥本事
Let's see what you got.
DDS总部    - WASHINGTON, D.C.
DIPLOMATIC SECURITY SERVICE HEADQUARTERS  - WASHINGTON, D.C.
你得看看这个
You need to look at that.
柏林 今天凌晨3点
Berlin, 3:00 a.m. this morning.
一队车手抢劫了一列军方车队
A team of drivers hijacked a military convoy.
Toretto? 不是
Toretto? Nope.
那我不感兴趣
I ain't interested.
不 你会感兴趣的  继续看
Yes, you are. Keep looking.
你相信鬼魂不?
Do you believe in ghosts?
交警叔叔提醒：本片当中的飞车场景相当危险
THE MOTOR VEHICLE ACTION SEQUENCES DEPICTED IN THIS FILM ARE DANGEROUS.
所有特技都在安全保护
ALL STUNTS WERE PERFORMED IN CONTROLLED ENVIRONMENTS
和专业人员在封闭路面完成
WITH PROFESSIONALLY TRAINED STUNT CREWS ON CLOSED ROADS.
切勿模仿
NO ATTEMPTS SHOULD BE MADE TO DUPLICATE ANY ACTION,
撞死活该
DRIVING OR CAR PLAY SCENES HEREIN PORTRAYED.